<resources xmlns:ns1="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Guide Key</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_title">Kavkaz</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_description">For decades Kavkaz established itself as one of the best spots for enjoyers of Caucasian cuisine in Yerevan. Its rustic decorations accommodate lively feasts and offer, also, small secluded rooms for romantic dinners. The vast menu offers a selection of authentic dishes from Armenian and Georgian cuisine and extensive range of regional wines.</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_address">4, 6 Teryan St</string>
    <string name="genacvale_title">Genatsvale</string>
    <string name="genacvale_description">A popular chain of Georgian restaurants that offers live music in some locations and a great menu of regional delicacies.</string>
    <string name="genacvale_address">7 Kievyan St</string>
    <string name="black_angus_title">Black Angus</string>
    <string name="black_angus_description">An up and coming premium burger restaurant that stands tall over its counterparts due to excellent service and delicious burgers.</string>
    <string name="black_angus_address">2/5 Abovyan St</string>
    <string name="sakurada_title">Sakurada</string>
    <string name="sakurada_description">Founded by Japanese, this quaint restaurant located underneath a staircase at the intersection of Abovyan and Nalbandyan. Sakurada is famous for its homemade udon noodles, but it has more than that to offer. Here I tried Omurice for the first time. </string>
    <string name="sakurada_address">23, 20 Nalbandyan St</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_title">Beer Academy</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_description">First craft beer restaurant in Yerevan, offering a small, yet refined selection of their own beer and assortment of delicious snacks and meals to go with it.</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_address">8 Moskovyan Street</string>
    <string name="dargett_title">Dargett</string>
    <string name="dargett_description">A restaurant of a new craft beer brand that offers a great selection of beer and amazing service.</string>
    <string name="dargett_address">72 Aram Street</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_title">Lovers\' Park</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_description">Formerly known as Pushkin\'s park, it was built in early 2010\'s, replacing rusty wrecks of amusement rides and unkempt trees and bushes with tidy alleys, flowerbeds and nice benches.</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_address">21 Marshal Baghramyan Ave</string>
    <string name="victory_park_title">Victory Park</string>
    <string name="victory_park_description">The biggest park in Yerevan, located behind the Cascade. Built to commemorate victory in WWII. The park contains a museum with WWII items displayed inside and vehicles of war displayed outside, an amusement park, a lake and many alleys.</string>
    <string name="victory_park_address">Azatutyan Ave</string>
    <string name="miniso_title">Miniso</string>
    <string name="miniso_description">A trendy store chain of a Japanese brand of cosmetics, small appliances and everyday items.</string>
    <string name="miniso_address">18/77, Northern Ave</string>
    <string name="tsiran_title">Tsiran Supermarket</string>
    <string name="tsiran_description">A supermarket chain that stands out with the quality of service, good planning, affordable prices and decent selection of products.</string>
    <string name="tsiran_address">2a Hrachya Kochar St</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_title">Rio Mall</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_description">A huge mall in the Arabkir district of Yerevan. It offers a wide range of shops, cafes and a cinema.</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_address">8 Vahram Papazyan St</string>
    <string name="vernissage_title">Vernissage</string>
    <string name="vernissage_description">On weekends, hundreds of painters and artisans display their work for tourists and locals in a park behind the Republic Square metro station. All kinds of hand-crafted curios, souvenirs and knick-knacks are available for purchase. The spot is especially popular with visiting diaspora to take a piece of homeland home with them. A part of the park is also used as a flea market.</string>
    <string name="vernissage_address">1, 3 Buzand St</string>
    <string name="cascade_title">Cascade</string>
    <string name="cascade_description">A unique city monument in the center city center. For the most part it\'s literally a kilometer-long cascade of stairs. Due to its ambition and hard times the country fell on during the last stages of its construction its top part still stands unfinished to this day. In early 2000s a diaspora billionaire Astafyan subsidised its renovation and to this day inside the complex a museum in his name is located inside. The museum also serves as means to travel up and down on escalators for free, giving the opportunity to admire the philanthropist\'s peculiar collection of modern art on display. The outside portion of the cascade serves as a park, which due to the great view it offers and proximity to city center is always busy, from top to bottom.</string>
    <string name="cascade_address">10 Tamanyan St</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_title">Northern Avenue</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_description">Constructed in late 2000\'s, this broadwalk connects Republic Square and Opera Square and unifies the city center. Packed with brand shops, business centers and fancy restaurants, it quickly became the most visited place in Yerevan.</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_address">Northern Avenue</string>
    <string name="metro_title">Metro</string>
    <string name="metro_description">It\'s only 10 stations long, but every station is a small architectural marvel with bold mix of avant-garde and classical designs. A convenient way to travel between most important parts of the city.</string>
    <string name="metro_address">Republic Square &amp; other places</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="bars_category">Bars</string>
    <string name="parks_category">Parks</string>
    <string name="shops_category">Shops</string>
    <string name="attractions_category">Other Attractions</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="yerevan_title">Yerevan</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_mycity">Welcome to MyCity!</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="main_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="tour_guide">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="start_onboarding"> Start Onboarding</string>
    <string name="yerevan_description">São Tomé and Príncipe, an African island nation close to the equator, is part of a volcano chain featuring striking rock and coral formations, rainforests and beaches. On the larger island, São Tomé, is the Lagoa Azul lagoon. Ôbo Natural Park, a biodiverse jungle preserve, covers much of São Tomé and is distinguished by Pico Cão Grande, a skyscraperlike volcanic rock</string>
    <string name="culture_content">Culture:São Tomé and Príncipe\'s culture is a vibrant mix of African and Portuguese influences. Music and dance, such as the Tchiloli and the Dêxa beat, are integral parts of their cultural heritage. The cuisine features seafood, tropical fruits, and dishes like calulu, a stew made with fish, palm oil, and vegetables. Traditional crafts include intricate wooden carvings, ceramics, and woven baskets. Festivals like the São João do Porto Alegre celebrate local traditions and religious events.\n</string>
    <string name="food_content">São Tomé and Príncipe\\\'s cuisine is a delightful blend of African, Portuguese, and Creole influences, reflecting the islands\\\' rich cultural history. The volcanic soil and tropical climate provide fertile ground for a variety of crops, ensuring a bounty of fresh ingredients. Staple foods include fish, seafood, and tropical fruits, with many dishes featuring coconut, banana, and plantain. Traditional meals often incorporate spices like piri-piri, cinnamon, and cloves, adding depth and flavor to the local cuisine. One of the most popular dishes is calulu, a hearty stew made with fish or chicken, mixed greens, and vegetables, cooked with palm oil and seasoned with local spices. Another favorite is moqueca, a fragrant fish stew simmered in coconut milk and seasoned with fresh herbs. Street food offers a variety of tasty snacks, such as fried bananas and grilled corn, perfect for a quick bite. São Tomé and Príncipe are also renowned for their cocoa production, producing some of the world\\\'s finest chocolate. Visitors can enjoy tours of cocoa plantations and indulge in exquisite chocolate treats, experiencing the islands\' sweet heritage firsthand. Overall, the cuisine of São Tomé and Príncipe is a testament to the islands\' natural abundance and cultural diversity, offering a delicious journey for any food enthusiast.</string>
    <string name="history_content">São Tomé and Príncipe, located off the western coast of Central Africa, were uninhabited until the Portuguese explorers arrived in the late 15th century. The islands were used for sugarcane plantations, worked by slaves brought from the African mainland. After the decline of the sugar industry, São Tomé and Príncipe became a major hub for cocoa production. In 1975, the islands gained independence from Portugal, becoming Africa\\\'s smallest Portuguese-speaking country.</string>
    <string name="history_title">A Brief History</string>
    <string name="culture_title">The Rich Culture of São Tomé</string>
    <string name="food_title">Flavors of São Tomé</string>

    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="follow_us">Follow Us</string>

    <string name="contact_us_fr">Nous contacter</string>
    <string name="email_fr">Courriel</string>
    <string name="phone_fr">Téléphone</string>
    <string name="address_fr">Adresse</string>
    <string name="follow_us_fr">Suivez-nous</string>
    <string name="contact_image_description">Contact Image Description</string>
    <string name="Qr_description">To be able to take a tour of our guide, you\'ll have to generate a code, which will take you to the SmartGuide application where you can access more information such as what to do, hotels, where to sleep, parties, where to eat, etc...</string>
    <string name="tour_guide_title">"Tour Guide "</string>


</resources>

